John H. Cornehlsen Papers 5730
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Psychological Profiles
  - Sub-Series A: Profiles done for Companies
    - Company CB Cases: Be, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Company CB Cases: Be, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Company CB Cases: Be, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Company CB Cases: Be, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Company CB Cases: Be, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Company CB Cases: Bi, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Company CB Cases: Bl, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Company CB Cases: Bo, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Company CB Cases: Bo, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Company CB Cases: Br, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Company CB Cases: Br, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Company CB Cases: Br, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Company CB Cases: Br, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Company CB Cases: Br, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Company CB Cases: Br, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Company CB Cases: Br, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Company CB Cases: Br, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Company CB Cases: Bu, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Company CB Cases: Bu, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Company CB Cases: Bu, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Company CB Cases: Bu, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Company CB Cases: Ca, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Company CB Cases: Ca, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Company CB Cases: Ca, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Company CB Cases: Ca, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Company CB Cases: Ca, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Company CB Cases: Ca (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Company CB Cases: Ca, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Company CB Cases: Ca, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Company CB Cases: Ca, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Company CB Cases: Ca, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Company CB Cases: Ch, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Company CB Cases: Ci, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Company CB Cases: Co, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Company CB Cases: Co, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Company CB Cases: Co, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Company CB Cases: Co, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Company CB Cases: De, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Company CB Cases: Do, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Company CB Cases: Er, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Company CB Cases: Fa, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Company CB Cases: Fa, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Company CB Cases: Fe, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Company CB Cases: Fe, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Company CB Cases: Fe, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Company CB Cases: Fi, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Company CB Cases: Fi, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Company CB Cases: Fi, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Company CB Cases: Fi, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Company CB Cases: Fr, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Company CB Cases: Fr, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Company CB Cases: Ga, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Company CB Cases: Gi, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Company CB Cases: Go, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Company CB Cases: Go, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Company CB Cases: Go, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Company CB Cases: Gr, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Company CB Cases: Gr, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Company CB Cases: Gr, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Company CB Cases: Gu, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Company CB Cases: Ha, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Company CB Cases: Ha, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Company CB Cases: He, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Company CB Cases: He, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Company CB Cases: He, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Company CB Cases: He, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Company CB Cases: Ho, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Company CB Cases: Hu, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Company CB Cases: Hu, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Company CB Cases: Hu, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Company CB Cases: Im, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Company CB Cases: Je, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Company CB Cases: Je, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Company CB Cases: Je, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Company CB Cases: Jo, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Company CB Cases: Jo, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Company CB Cases: Ka, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Company CB Cases: Ka, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Company CB Cases: Ke, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Company CB Cases: Ke, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Company CB Cases: Ke, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Company CB Cases: Ke, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Company CB Cases: Ke, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Company CB Cases: Kl, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Company CB Cases: Ko, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Company CB Cases: Kr, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Company CB Cases: Ku, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Company CB Cases: La, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Company CB Cases: La, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Company CB Cases: La, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Company CB Cases: Le, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Company CB Cases: Li, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Company CB Cases: Li, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Company CB Cases: Lo, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Company CB Cases: Ma, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Company CB Cases: Ma, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Company CB Cases: Mc, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Company CB Cases: Mc, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Company CB Cases: Mc, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Company CB Cases: Mc, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Company CB Cases: Me, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Company CB Cases: Mi, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Company CB Cases: Mi, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Company CB Cases: Mo, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Company CB Cases: Na, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Company CB Cases: Ne, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Company CB Cases: Ne, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Company CB Cases: Nu, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Company CB Cases: Og, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Company CB Cases: Os, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Company CB Cases: Os, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Company CB Cases: Pa, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Company CB Cases: Po, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Company CB Cases: Po, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Company CB Cases: Pr, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Company CB Cases: Ra (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Company CB Cases: Re, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Company CB Cases: Ro, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Company CB Cases: He, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Company CB Cases: Sa, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Company CB Cases: Sc, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Company CB Cases: Sc, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Company CB Cases: Sc, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Company CB Cases: Sc, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Company CB Cases: Se, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Company CB Cases: Se, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Company CB Cases: Se, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Company CB Cases: Sh, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Company CB Cases: Sh, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Company CB Cases: Si, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Company CB Cases: Si, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Company CB Cases: Sk, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Company CB Cases: Sm, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Company CB Cases: St, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Company CB Cases: St, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Company CB Cases: St, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Company CB Cases: St, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Company CB Cases: Sw, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Company CB Cases: Ta, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Company CB Cases: Ti, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Company CB Cases: Th, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Company CB Cases: Tr, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Company CB Cases: Tu, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Company CB Cases: Ul, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Company CB Cases: Va, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Company CB Cases: Va, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Company CB Cases: Wa, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Company CB Cases: We, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Company CB Cases: Wh, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Company CB Cases: Wo, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Company CB Cases: Wr, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Company CB Cases: Wr, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Company CB Cases: Wy, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Company CB Cases: Yo, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Company CB Cases: Yo, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Company CB Cases: Yo, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Company CB Cases: Zi, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series B: Profiles done for Individuals
    - Individual Files: 4-A to 43-A (Box 35, Folder 43)
      Code: 4A-43A
    - Individual Files: Ab, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Individual Files: Ad, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Individual Files: Ad, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Individual Files: Al, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Individual Files: Al, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Individual Files: An, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Individual Files: An, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Individual Files: An, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Individual Files: An, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Individual Files: 3-B to 21-B (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Code: 3B-21B
    - Individual Files: 22-B to 45-B (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Code: 22-B - 45-B
    - Individual Files: 46-B to 70-B (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Code: 46B-70B
    - Individual Files: 71-B to 87-B (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Code: 71B-87B
    - Individual Files: 88-B to 108-B (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Code: 88B-108B
    - Individual Files: Ba, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Individual Files: Ba (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Individual Files: Ba, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Individual Files: Ba, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      Code: 82B
    - Individual Files: Ba, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Individual Files: Ba, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Individual Files: Ba, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Individual Files: Ba, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Individual Files: Ba, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Individual Files: Ba, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      Code: 84B
    - Individual Files: Be, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Individual Files: Be, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Individual Files: Be, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Individual Files: Be, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Individual Files: Be, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Individual Files: Be, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Individual Files: Be, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Individual Files: Bl, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Individual Files: Bl, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Individual Files: Bo, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Individual Files: Bo, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Individual Files: Bo, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Individual Files: Bo, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Individual Files: Bo, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Individual Files: Bo, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Individual Files: Bo, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Individual Files: Br, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Individual Files: Br, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Individual Files: Br, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Individual Files: Br, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Individual Files: Br, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Individual Files: Br, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Individual Files: Br, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Individual Files: Br, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Individual Files: Br, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      Code: 85B
    - Individual Files: Br, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Individual Files: Bu, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Individual Files: Bu, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Individual Files: Bu, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Individual Files: 1-C to 24-C (Box 37, Folder 7)
      Code: 1C-24C
    - Individual Files: 25-C to 48-C (Box 37, Folder 8)
      Code: 25C-48C
    - Individual Files: 49-C to 63-C (Box 37, Folder 9)
      Code: 49C-63C
    - Individual Files: 64-C to 77-C (Box 37, Folder 10)
      Code: 64C-77C
    - Individual Files: Ca (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Individual Files: Ca, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Individual Files: Ca, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Individual Files: Ca, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Individual Files: Ca, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Individual Files: Ca (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Individual Files: Ca, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Individual Files: Ca (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Individual Files: Ch (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Individual Files: Ch, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Individual Files: Ch, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      Code: 50C
    - Individual Files: Cl (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Individual Files: Cl, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      Code: 33A
    - Individual Files: Cl, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Individual Files: Cl, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      Code: 18C
    - Individual Files: Co, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Individual Files: Co, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Individual Files: Co, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Individual Files: Co, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Individual Files: Co, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Individual Files: Cr, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Individual Files: Cr, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      Code: 75C
    - Individual Files: 3-D to 20-D (Box 37, Folder 33)
      Code: 3D-20D
    - Individual Files: 21-D to 43-D (Box 37, Folder 34)
      Code: 21D-43D
    - Individual Files: 45-D to 62-D (Box 37, Folder 35)
      Code: 45D-62D
    - Individual Files: Da, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Individual Files: Da, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Individual Files: Da (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Individual Files: Da, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Individual Files: Da, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Individual Files: Da, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Individual Files: Da, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Individual Files: Da, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Individual Files: De, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Individual Files: De, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Individual Files: De, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Individual Files: De, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Individual Files: De (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Individual Files: De, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Individual Files: De, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Individual Files: Di, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Individual Files: Di (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Individual Files: Di, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Individual Files: Di (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Individual Files: Do, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Individual Files: Do (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Individual Files: Dr (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Individual Files: 1-E to 14-E (Box 38, Folder 17)
      Code: 1E-14E
    - Individual Files: 15-E to 25-E (Box 38, Folder 18)
      Code: 15E-25E
    - Individual Files: Ed (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Individual Files: Eg (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Individual Files: Er (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Individual Files: 1-F to 16-F (Box 38, Folder 22)
      Code: 1F-16F
    - Individual Files: 17-F to 36-F (Box 38, Folder 23)
      Code: 17F-36F
    - Individual Files: Fa (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Individual Files: Fe (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Individual Files: Fi, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Individual Files: Fi (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Individual Files: Fl (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Individual Files: Fo, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Individual Files: 3-G to 20-G (Box 38, Folder 30)
      Code: 3G-20G
    - Individual Files: 21-G to 41-G (Box 38, Folder 31)
      Cose: 21G-41G
    - Individual Files: Ga, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Individual Files: Ga, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Individual Files: Ga (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Individual Files: Ga (Box 38, Folder 35)
      Coode: 32G
    - Individual Files: Ga, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Individual Files: Ga, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Individual Files: Ge (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Individual Files: Ge, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Individual Files: Gi, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Individual Files: Gi (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Individual Files: Go (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Individual Files: Go, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Individual Files: Gr, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Individual Files: Gr (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Individual Files: Gr, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Individual Files: Gr, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Individual Files: Gr (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Individual Files: Gr, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Individual Files: Gr (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Individual Files: Gr, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Individual Files: Gr, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Individual Files: Gr, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Individual Files: Gu, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Individual Files: 7-H to 20-H (Box 39, Folder 14)
      Code: 7H-20H
    - Individual Files: 21-H to 44-H (Box 39, Folder 15)
      Code: 21H-44H
    - Individual Files: 42-H to 60-H (Box 39, Folder 16)
      Code: 42H-60H
    - Individual Files: 61-H to 78-H (Box 39, Folder 17)
      Code: 61H-78H
    - Individual Files: 79-H to 94-H (Box 39, Folder 18)
      Code: 79H-94H
    - Individual Files: Ha (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Individual Files: Ha (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Individual Files: Ha (Box 39, Folder 21)
      Code: 66H
    - Individual Files: Ha, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Individual Files: Ha (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Individual Files: Ha, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Individual Files: Ha (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Individual Files: Ha (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Individual Files: Ha, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Individual Files: Ha (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Individual Files: Ha, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Individual Files: Ha (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Individual Files: Ha, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Individual Files: Ha, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Individual Files: Ha (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Individual Files: Ha, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Individual Files: He (Box 39, Folder 35)
      Code: 68H
    - Individual Files: He, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Individual Files: He (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Individual Files: Hi (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Individual Files: Hi (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Individual Files: Ho, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Individual Files: Ho, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Individual Files: Ho, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Individual Files: Ho, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Individual Files: Ho, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Individual Files: Ho (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Individual Files: Ho (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Individual Files: Hu (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Individual Files: 1-I to 5-I (Box 40, Folder 7)
      Code: 1L-5L
    - Individual Files: In, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Individual Files: In, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Individual Files: 1-J to 25-J (Box 40, Folder 10)
      Code: 1J-25J
    - Individual Files: Ja (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Individual Files: Ja (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Individual Files: Je (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Individual Files: Jo, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Individual Files: Jo, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Individual Files: Jo, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Individual Files: 5-K to 26-K (Box 40, Folder 17)
      Code: 5K-26K
    - Individual Files: 27-K to 49-K (Box 40, Folder 18)
      Code: 27K-49K
    - Individual Files: 50-K to 53-K (Box 40, Folder 19)
      Code: 50K-53K
    - Individual Files: Ka (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Individual Files: Ka (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Individual Files: Ka (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Individual Files: Ka, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Individual Files: Ke, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Individual Files: Ke (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Individual Files: Ke, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Individual Files: Ke (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Individual Files: Ke, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Individual Files: Ki, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Individual Files: Kl (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Individual Files: Kl, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Individual Files: Kn, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Individual Files: Kn (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Individual Files: Ko, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Individual Files: Ko, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Individual Files: Kr, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Individual Files: Kr (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Individual Files: Kr (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Individual Files: Kr, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Individual Files: Kw, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Individual Files: 2-L to 12-L (Box 40, Folder 41)
      Code: 2L-12L
    - 1Individual Files: 3-L to 37-L (Box 40, Folder 42)
      Code: 13L-37L
    - Individual Files: 39-L to 57-L (Box 40, Folder 43)
      Code: 39L-57L
    - Individual Files: 58-L to 70-L (Box 40, Folder 44)
      Code: 58L-70L
    - Individual Files: La, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Individual Files: La (Box 41, Folder 2)
      Code: 47L
    - Individual Files: La, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Individual Files: La (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Individual Files: La, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Individual Files: Le (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Individual Files: Le, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Individual Files: Le, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Individual Files: Le, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Individual Files: Le, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Individual Files: Le, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Individual Files: Li, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Individual Files: Li, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Individual Files: Li, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Individual Files: Li, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Individual Files: Lo, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Individual Files: Lo (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Individual Files: Lo, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Individual Files: Lo, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Individual Files: Lu, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Individual Files: Ly (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Individual Files: 4-M to 22-M (Box 41, Folder 22)
      Code: 4M-22M
    - Individual Files: 23-M to 52-M (Box 41, Folder 23)
      Code: 23M-52M
    - Individual Files: 53-M to 87-M (Box 41, Folder 24)
      Code: 53M-87M
    - Individual Files: 88-M to 115-M (Box 41, Folder 25)
      Code: 88M-115M
    - Individual Files: 116-M to 125-M (Box 41, Folder 26)
      Code: 116M-125M
    - Individual Files: Ma (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Individual Files: Ma, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Individual Files: Ma (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Individual Files: Ma (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Individual Files: Ma, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Individual Files: Ma, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Individual Files: Ma, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Individual Files: Ma, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Individual Files: Ma, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Individual Files: Ma (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Individual Files: Ma (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Individual Files: Ma, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Individual Files: Ma, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Individual Files: Ma, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Individual Files: Ma, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Individual Files: Mc (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Individual Files: Mc, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Individual Files: Mc, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Individual Files: Mc, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Individual Files: Mc (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Individual Files: Mc (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Individual Files: Me (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Individual Files: Me, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Individual Files: Me, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Individual Files: Me (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Individual Files: Mi, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Individual Files: Mi, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Individual Files: Mi (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Individual Files: Mi, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Individual Files: Mo (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Individual Files: Mo, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Individual Files: Mu, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Individual Files: Mu (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Individual Files: Mu (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Individual Files: Me, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Individual Files: 1-N to 30-N (Box 42, Folder 24)
      Code: 1N-30N
    - Individual Files: Na (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Individual Files: Ne, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Individual Files: No, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Individual Files: Nu (Box 42, Folder 28)